https://www.lloydmcgill.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Notice for Customers and Training Participants
Lloyd McGill, the Training Provider, consultancy service provider, auditing organisation and/or their respective affiliates respect the privacy of all our customers and training participants, and are committed to safeguarding the personal information you provide to us. Please read this Privacy (“Policy“) to learn about how Lloyd McGill collects, uses and protects your personal information.
Application of Policy
This Policy is based on the Singapore Personal Data Protection Act 2012 and all the associated regulations and guidelines which may from time to time be issued by the Personal Data Protection Commission of Singapore.
This Policy applies to all data in any form about an individual who can be identified from that data which are in our possession or under our control for the purposes of and in connection with our contractual duties and provision of our services.
Under the Singapore Personal Data Protection Act 2012, business contact information (e.g. name, business address, business telephone number) is not considered as personal data so long as it is used strictly for business-to-business (B2B) transactions.
Collection of Personal Data
We collect data that you voluntarily provide to us (primarily business contact information such as your name, job title, company name, company address, company contact number and company e-mail address) when you enquire about our services via email, telephone or through our website. The information you provide will be handled according to this Privacy Policy.
Personal data are collected in relation to the provision of our training services, and this includes:
Participant Full name
Participant Email
Participant Designation
You have choices regarding our collection, use or disclosure of your personal data. You have the right to object to the processing of your personal data and withdraw your consent in a manner described in clause 5 below.
We may collect, disclose or use your personal data pursuant to an exception under the Personal Data Protection Act or other written law such as during the following situations:
To respond to an emergency that threatens your life, health and safety or of another individual; and
Necessary in the national interest, for any investigation or proceedings.
In general, subject to the applicable exceptions permitted in the Singapore Personal Data Protection Act 2012, before we collect the above personal data from you, we will notify you of the purposes for which your personal data may be collected, used and/or disclosed, as well as obtain your consent for the collection, use and/or disclosure of your personal data for the intended purposes. If you choose not to provide us with the personal data described in this Policy, we may not be able to fulfil our contractual duties towards you or facilitate your request or provide the service to you.
Cookies
Our website uses cookies to improve your browsing experience. The cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyse and understand how you use our website generally, recognize your repeat visits and preferences, as well as to measure and analyse traffic.
These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. By clicking “Accept” on our cookie banner, or if you continue to explore our site without changing your cookie settings (link provided in the cookie banner), you consent to the use of cookies on our website. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies by changing your cookie settings anytime. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Use of Personal Data Collected
Any Personal Data provided by you to us may be used for the following purposes (where relevant):
Process and respond to your requests and queries;
Send you information, updates, invitations, marketing and advertising materials and information in relation to the training, consultancy or auditing services (or future editions thereof) or any other workshops/activities held by Lloyd McGill, its partners and/or their respective affiliates;
Update our records;
Process your personal particulars to facilitate any payment;
Compile data and conduct statistical or demographic analysis;
Solicit and record your opinion/feedback via surveys and requests for feedback (if you consent to participating);
Comply with a court order, other legal processes or other legal requirements of any governmental authority (including detecting, investigating and preventing any crime, offence or breaches);
Comply with our internal policies/procedures and any applicable laws, rules and regulations, codes of practice, guidelines and any other legal purposes; and
Allow us to use your Personal Data in any other ways for which we have notified you and obtained your consent accordingly.
Disclosure of Personal Data
All Personal Data held by us will be kept confidential, but we may, where such disclosure is necessary to satisfy the purpose, or a directly-related purpose for which the Personal Data was collected as described in section 3 and 4 above, provide such information to the following parties:
Any person or company who is acting for, jointly or on our behalf, in respect of the purpose or a directly-related purpose for which the Personal Data was provided;
Any financial institutions, charge or credit card issuing companies, credit bureau, or collection agencies necessary to establish and support the payment of any services due or requested; and
Any government authority in compliance with any applicable laws, rules and regulations, codes of practices, guidelines, court order, other legal processes or requirements.
Withdrawal of Consent
The consent that you provide for the collection, use and disclosure of your personal data will remain valid until such time it is being withdrawn by you in writing. Should you wish to withdraw your consent, you may send us the appropriate withdrawal request by filling up the Consent Withdrawal Form below and sending the same to our Data Protection Officer at enquiry@lloydmcgill.com. Please note that we can only process Consent Withdrawal Forms that are properly filled up and may need to contact you for clarification if such forms are deemed to be incomplete or unclear in any way. Please understand that your withdrawal of consent for purposes necessary to Lloyd McGill fulfilling our contractual duties towards you or facilitating your request or providing our services to you may carry consequences. We will review and inform you on the consequences of the withdrawal prior to processing your request.
Access and Correction of Personal Data
If you wish to access, update or otherwise change or remove any information that you have provided to us, you may send us your request using the Access Request Form and Correction Form below and sending the same to our Data Protection Officer at enquiry@lloydmcgill.com.
An administration fee may be charged for the handling and processing of your request to access your personal data. If so, we will inform you of the fee beforehand.
Accuracy of Personal Data
We will take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal data we collect about you is accurate, complete, not misleading and kept up-to-date, taking into account its intended use. Where possible, we will validate the Personal Data provided by you using generally accepted practices and guidelines.
Protection of Personal Data
We employ appropriate administrative, physical, technical and organizational security measures to help protect your personal data against loss and to guard against unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification, regardless of the format in which it is held.
Retention of Personal Data
We will retain your Personal Data only for as long as the purposes for which such data is collected or used (as notified to you) continues, or where necessary, for our legal or business purposes. We will dispose of or destroy/delete documents containing your personal data in a secure manner when the retention limit described in our Retention and Destruction Policy is reached or as soon as it is reasonable to assume that the permitted purpose is no longer being served by their retention.
Any unsolicited personal data received by us will be returned to the sender immediately. If received by email or through our website, these unsolicited personal data will be deleted right away. If received by telephone, these will not be recorded.
Changes to Policy
We reserve the right to modify or change this Policy at any time and will place such amendments on this website.
This Policy applies in conjunction with contractual clauses and consent clauses that apply in relation to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal data by us. Your continued use of our services constitutes your acknowledgement and acceptance of this Policy and any such changes.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or feedback regarding this Policy, you may contact our Data Protection Officer at enquiry@lloydmcgill.com.
If you have any complaint relating to how we manage your personal data, you may send it to us via the email address above using the Complaint Form below.
Forms for download
Complaint Action Form Download
Correction Request Form Download
Access Request Form Download
Consent Withdrawal Form Download
Enquire Now
Scroll
×
Enquire Now
ConsultancyGeneral enquiryData Protection MattersCourses & ScheduleFeedback
It is our responsibility/ to ensure that your data is protected, and you can be assured that we will never sell, rent or forward your personal data to a third party. It is part of our Privacy Policy, and the personal data you provide to us will only be used through permissions explicitly granted by you under our Terms and Conditions
I hereby agree and consent to Lloyd McGill Pte Ltd Terms & Conditions and the Privacy Policy.
×
Terms & Conditions
TERMS & CONDITIONS
These Terms and Conditions (“Terms and Conditions”) govern your use as a user (the “User”) of the website and all its webpages thereunder (excluding any third party content) (the “Website”) which is managed by Lloyd McGill Pte. Ltd. (“LM”). By accessing and using the Website, the User agrees to be bound by the Terms and Conditions. If the User does not agree with any of the Terms and Conditions contained within, please discontinue using the Website.
Accessing the Website
LM does not guarantee continuous accessibility or uninterrupted operation of the Website and shall not be held liable, if for any reason, any information is or becomes unavailable at any time or for any period. LM do not warrant or represent that any information transmitted via electronic mail or the Website to/from the User will be accurately received or is secure.
Variation
LM reserves the right to withdraw or vary any of the Terms and Conditions of the Website and/or any part of or information contained in the Website without any prior notice.
Use and Reliance
The use of the Website and the electronic transmission of any document or information to/from the User via the Website are entirely at the User’s own risk. LM does not warrant the accuracy or completeness of the information or the reliability of any advice, opinion, statement and/or other information contained in the Website and any reliance thereof shall also be entirely at the User’s own risk. The User should make his/her own checks, consult an appropriate professional for specific advice and/or rely on his/her own judgment.
Content of Third Party Websites
LM is not responsible for, and do not necessarily endorse, the content of any third party websites which may be linked from the Website out of convenience.
Limitations of Use
The User may not copy, display, distribute, modify, publish, reproduce, transmit and/or otherwise transfer any content obtained from the Website for any commercial purpose without LM’s prior written consent.
The User may not use the Website for any unlawful purpose or in such manner as prohibited by the Terms and Conditions, particularly:
(a) using the Website in any manner that could negatively affect the Website or the network connected thereto (including but not limited to damaging, impairing, interfering with or overburdening the Website (in whole or in part));
(b) gaining unauthorised access to the Website and the network connected thereto (including by way of hacking or password theft); and
(c) obtaining any information which is not intended by LM to be made available via the Website at that time.
Disclaimer and Exclusion of Liability
While LM endeavours to use reasonable efforts to ensure accuracy in the information presented on the Website, LM hereby disclaims all warranties and representations (express or implied), to the fullest extent permissible under the law, as to the accuracy, availability, completeness, timeliness, veracity and any other aspects of the information contained on the Website. LM assumes no responsibility for all the content on the Website which are provided on an “as is” and “as available” basis, and may contain inaccuracies and/or typographical errors. LM also does not warrant or represent that the Website will be free from any virus or other malicious, destructive or corrupting code, agent, program or macros.
LM and its affiliates hereby excludes their liability, to the fullest extent permissible under the law, for any direct, indirect, special or consequential damage or loss arising from any inability to access the Website, any use of the Website and/or any reliance on the information contained in the Website (including the Terms and Conditions) and any variation thereof, by the User.
Copyright and Intellectual Property Rights
All the content on the Website (including but not limited to text, graphics, photographs, logos, icons, videos and sounds) is copyrighted and may not be used without the prior written permission of LM. LM also does not warrant that the use of information contained in the Website will not infringe the intellectual property or other rights of third parties.
Indemnification
The User agrees to indemnify, defend and hold harmless LM, its affiliates, directors, employees, agents, successors or assigns from any losses, claims, demands, liability, costs, expenses, actions or threat of action arising from or in connection with the User’s breach the Terms and Conditions and/or in connection with the User’s use of the Website unless LM is liable due to its own default, negligence or breach of any laws.
Governing Law
The Terms and Conditions are governed by the laws of Singapore.
Close
×
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Notice for Customers and Training Participants
Lloyd McGill, the Training Provider, consultancy service provider, auditing organisation and/or their respective affiliates respect the privacy of all our customers and training participants, and are committed to safeguarding the personal information you provide to us. Please read this Privacy (“Policy“) to learn about how Lloyd McGill collects, uses and protects your personal information.
Application of Policy
This Policy is based on the Singapore Personal Data Protection Act 2012 and all the associated regulations and guidelines which may from time to time be issued by the Personal Data Protection Commission of Singapore.
This Policy applies to all data in any form about an individual who can be identified from that data which are in our possession or under our control for the purposes of and in connection with our contractual duties and provision of our services.
Under the Singapore Personal Data Protection Act 2012, business contact information (e.g. name, business address, business telephone number) is not considered as personal data so long as it is used strictly for business-to-business (B2B) transactions.
Collection of Personal Data
We collect data that you voluntarily provide to us (primarily business contact information such as your name, job title, company name, company address, company contact number and company e-mail address) when you enquire about our services via email, telephone or through our website. The information you provide will be handled according to this Privacy Policy.
Personal data are collected in relation to the provision of our training services, and this includes:
Participant Full name
Participant Email
Participant Designation
You have choices regarding our collection, use or disclosure of your personal data. You have the right to object to the processing of your personal data and withdraw your consent in a manner described in clause 5 below.
We may collect, disclose or use your personal data pursuant to an exception under the Personal Data Protection Act or other written law such as during the following situations:
To respond to an emergency that threatens your life, health and safety or of another individual; and
Necessary in the national interest, for any investigation or proceedings.
In general, subject to the applicable exceptions permitted in the Singapore Personal Data Protection Act 2012, before we collect the above personal data from you, we will notify you of the purposes for which your personal data may be collected, used and/or disclosed, as well as obtain your consent for the collection, use and/or disclosure of your personal data for the intended purposes. If you choose not to provide us with the personal data described in this Policy, we may not be able to fulfil our contractual duties towards you or facilitate your request or provide the service to you.
Cookies
Our website uses cookies to improve your browsing experience. The cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyse and understand how you use our website generally, recognize your repeat visits and preferences, as well as to measure and analyse traffic.
These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. By clicking “Accept” on our cookie banner, or if you continue to explore our site without changing your cookie settings (link provided in the cookie banner), you consent to the use of cookies on our website. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies by changing your cookie settings anytime. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Use of Personal Data Collected
Any Personal Data provided by you to us may be used for the following purposes (where relevant):
Process and respond to your requests and queries;
Send you information, updates, invitations, marketing and advertising materials and information in relation to the training, consultancy or auditing services (or future editions thereof) or any other workshops/activities held by Lloyd McGill, its partners and/or their respective affiliates;
Update our records;
Process your personal particulars to facilitate any payment;
Compile data and conduct statistical or demographic analysis;
Solicit and record your opinion/feedback via surveys and requests for feedback (if you consent to participating);
Comply with a court order, other legal processes or other legal requirements of any governmental authority (including detecting, investigating and preventing any crime, offence or breaches);
Comply with our internal policies/procedures and any applicable laws, rules and regulations, codes of practice, guidelines and any other legal purposes; and
Allow us to use your Personal Data in any other ways for which we have notified you and obtained your consent accordingly.
Disclosure of Personal Data
All Personal Data held by us will be kept confidential, but we may, where such disclosure is necessary to satisfy the purpose, or a directly-related purpose for which the Personal Data was collected as described in section 3 and 4 above, provide such information to the following parties:
Any person or company who is acting for, jointly or on our behalf, in respect of the purpose or a directly-related purpose for which the Personal Data was provided;
Any financial institutions, charge or credit card issuing companies, credit bureau, or collection agencies necessary to establish and support the payment of any services due or requested; and
Any government authority in compliance with any applicable laws, rules and regulations, codes of practices, guidelines, court order, other legal processes or requirements.
Withdrawal of Consent
The consent that you provide for the collection, use and disclosure of your personal data will remain valid until such time it is being withdrawn by you in writing. Should you wish to withdraw your consent, you may send us the appropriate withdrawal request by filling up the Consent Withdrawal Form below and sending the same to our Data Protection Officer at enquiry@lloydmcgill.com. Please note that we can only process Consent Withdrawal Forms that are properly filled up and may need to contact you for clarification if such forms are deemed to be incomplete or unclear in any way. Please understand that your withdrawal of consent for purposes necessary to Lloyd McGill fulfilling our contractual duties towards you or facilitating your request or providing our services to you may carry consequences. We will review and inform you on the consequences of the withdrawal prior to processing your request.
Access and Correction of Personal Data
If you wish to access, update or otherwise change or remove any information that you have provided to us, you may send us your request using the Access Request Form and Correction Form below and sending the same to our Data Protection Officer at enquiry@lloydmcgill.com.
An administration fee may be charged for the handling and processing of your request to access your personal data. If so, we will inform you of the fee beforehand.
Accuracy of Personal Data
We will take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal data we collect about you is accurate, complete, not misleading and kept up-to-date, taking into account its intended use. Where possible, we will validate the Personal Data provided by you using generally accepted practices and guidelines.
Protection of Personal Data
We employ appropriate administrative, physical, technical and organizational security measures to help protect your personal data against loss and to guard against unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification, regardless of the format in which it is held.
Retention of Personal Data
We will retain your Personal Data only for as long as the purposes for which such data is collected or used (as notified to you) continues, or where necessary, for our legal or business purposes. We will dispose of or destroy/delete documents containing your personal data in a secure manner when the retention limit described in our Retention and Destruction Policy is reached or as soon as it is reasonable to assume that the permitted purpose is no longer being served by their retention.
Any unsolicited personal data received by us will be returned to the sender immediately. If received by email or through our website, these unsolicited personal data will be deleted right away. If received by telephone, these will not be recorded.
Changes to Policy
We reserve the right to modify or change this Policy at any time and will place such amendments on this website.
This Policy applies in conjunction with contractual clauses and consent clauses that apply in relation to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal data by us. Your continued use of our services constitutes your acknowledgement and acceptance of this Policy and any such changes.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or feedback regarding this Policy, you may contact our Data Protection Officer at enquiry@lloydmcgill.com.
If you have any complaint relating to how we manage your personal data, you may send it to us via the email address above using the Complaint Form below.
Forms for download
Complaint Action Form Download
Correction Request Form Download
Access Request Form Download
Consent Withdrawal Form Download
Close
This site uses cookies to help us serve you better. By continuing to explore our site, you accept our use of cookies.
Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
